<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SAS on Kai Chang</title>
    <link>https://kaichang97.github.io/tags/sas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SAS on Kai Chang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kaichang97.github.io/tags/sas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SAS Optimization Challenge</title>
      <link>https://kaichang97.github.io/post/sas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaichang97.github.io/post/sas/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Building T currently receives their water through two sources: the Water Company and their ownXYZ Water Storage Tank. The company is currently deciding which Water Company contract to sign.
Problem Statement Which of the two proposed contracts provides XYZ Corporation with the lowest total water cost over the next four weeks?
Results Demand Forecasting   Contract 2 will have a lower cost based on our demand forecasting. By selecting the recommended contract over the alternative contract, XYZ will save $3,921.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classification Algorithms to Forecast if a User Will Default Credit Card Payment</title>
      <link>https://kaichang97.github.io/post/creditcard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaichang97.github.io/post/creditcard/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview Credit Default forecast has been a subject of interest for every credit card company, and the accurate prediction on default can balance the lenders&#39; risk and return. Based on users&#39; historical and demographical information, lenders can modify their policy to the borrowers such as charging a higher rate for higher risks.
Overall speaking, the aim of predicting credit default is to develop a predictive model that utilizes historical payment status and certain demographical information to evaluate the likeliness of credit default</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
